Richard York Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artists' Artwork Files, circa 1865-2004, Series 2:; (Boxes 7-64; 56.85 linear feet)
  - General, circa 1865-2004, 2.1:
    - Butler, Theodore Earl, 5072CY: Portrait of the Artist William Howard Hart, Giverny, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Butler, Theodore Earl, 5074CY: Suzanne and Jimmy, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Butler, Theodore Earl, 5075LY: Le Bain, Maison Baptiste or The Bath, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Butler, Theodore Earl, 5076LY, Chemin des Ajoux, Giverny, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Butler, Theodore Earl, 5079CY: [Le Bain, Maison Baptiste] The Bath, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Butler, Theodore Earl, 6876CY: Summer Garden With Sweet Peas, 1997, 2001, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Buttersworth, James Edward, 1938CY: Catboats off the Coast, 1987, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Buttersworth, James Edward, 2201CY: Off the Coast, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Buttersworth, James Edward, 2532CY: Flying Cloud off the Needles, 1988-1994 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Buttersworth, James Edward, 3286CY: Governors Island with Yachting, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Buttersworth, James Edward, 3447CY: Black Squall at Gibraltar, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Buttersworth, T. (Attributed), 4065LY: Frigates at Sea, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Buzzell, Taylor, 7743RY: Still Life of Apples in a Silver Compote, 2001, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Cahill, William Vincent, 4025CY: Flatiron Building, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Cahill, William Vincent, 4026CY: Plaza Hotel, New York, from Central Park at Moonlight, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Calder, Alexander, 2723JY: Sign Writers' Red, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Calder, Alexander, 6994CY: Red Crest of the Wave, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Calder, Alexander, 7099CY: Wire Sculpture, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Calyo, Nicolino, 4022CY: View of the Great Fire in New York, 1835, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Calyo, Nicolino, 4023CY: View of the Ruin after the Great Fire in New York, 1835, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 1155CY: After the Bath, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 1433RY: Still Life, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 1846CY: Mrs. Carles and Sara, 1986-1989, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 1847CY: Study for Flower Composition, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 2025CY: Flowers or Abstract Still-Life, 1987-1992 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 2603CY: Still Life, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 2909CY: Italian Landscape, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 3274CY: Tulips in a Vase, 1991-1994 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 3682CY: Bouquet of Flowers, 1992-1998 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 3718CY: Angèle, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 3921CY (second): Angèle, 1993, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 3922CY: Study for Last Painting, Abstract Still Life, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 4140CY: Dancers, 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 4379CY: Nude, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 5049CY: Sails, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6033CY: Abstract Composition, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6034CY: Fruit and Flowers, 1997, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6035CY: Group of Five Figures, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6036CY: Nude on Sofa with Vase of Flowers, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6037CY: Still Life with Flowered Cloth, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6038CY: Reclining Nude, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6039CY: Still Life with Chrysanthemums, 1997, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6040CY: Still Life with Fruit, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6041CY: Vase of Flowers, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6046RY: Vase of Flowers, 1997, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6061LY: Flowers, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6062LY: Flowers or Abstract Still Life, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6063LY: Chamonix, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6064LY: Green Nude, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6065LY: French Village Church, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher (Attributed), 6066CY: "Impressionist" Church, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher (Attributed), 6067CY: Still Life with Blue Ribbon, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6087CY: Pheasant with Green Apple, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6088CY: Portrait of Katherine Rhoades, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6089CY: Sunflower Abstraction, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6091JY: Flowers, Still Life, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6093LY: At the Opera, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6135CY: Flower Abstraction, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6359CY: Self-Portrait, 1998, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6630CY: Man at the Piano (Leopold Stokowski), 1998 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 6839CY: The Harpist, 6840CY: Portrait of Caroline, 1998-2004 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 7648CY: Still Life, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 7728CY: Sunflower Abstraction, 1997, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 9150CY: Man at the Piano (Leopold Stokowski), 2003 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Carlsen, Emil, 1199CY: Landscape, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Carlsen, Emil, 1206CY: The Idol, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Carlsen, Emil, 1768RY: Pumpkins, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Carlsen, Emil, 1881CY: Connecticut Landscape, circa 1986 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Carlsen, Emil, 3945CY: Skagen, 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Carlsen, Emil, 4469CY: Sunlit Landscape, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Carlsen, Emil, 4929CY: The Open Sea, 1996-2001 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - Carlsen, Emil, 6874CY: Cherry Tree, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 79)
    - Carlsen, Emil, 7054CY: Sunlit Landscape, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 80)
    - Carlsen, Emil, 7460CY: Chrysanthemums in a Vase, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - Carlsen, Emil, 8169CY: Cherry Tree, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Carlson, John Fabian, 173CY: Winter Landscape, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Carlson, John Fabian, 2329RY: Hillside Farm, 1988-1995 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - Carminecke, John Herman, 6057CY: Lake George, Adirondacks, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Carolus-Duran, [Emile Auguste], 6859CY: Bouquet of Flowers, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Carolus-Duran, Emile Auguste, 6860CY: View of Venice, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 87)
    - Carolus-Duran, [Emile Auguste], 7739CY: Arc de Fleurs [Bouquet of Flowers], 2001- 2002 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - Carr, Samuel S.: First Pony Ride at Coney Island, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - Carr, Samuel S., 751LY: Child Playing, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Carr, Samuel S., 1426CY: Pic-Nic, Prospect Park, Brooklyn, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - Carr, Samuel S., 6245RY: The Blacksmith's Shop, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Carr, Samuel S., 8382CY: On the Beach at Coney Island, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Casilear, John William, 138CY: Landscape with Cows, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Casilear, John William, 220CY: Figure on a Hillside, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Casilear, John William, 1665CY: Grand Tetons, Jackson Lake, Wyoming, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Casilear, John William, 1716CY: Morning on Lake George, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Casilear, John William, 1742CY: Rocky Mountain Landscape, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Casilear, John William, 4148CY: Twilight, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Casilear, John William, 4243CY: White Mountains, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Casilear, John William, 4318LY: Swiss Mountain Landscape, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Casilear, John William, 7044JY: Man on a Country Road, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 304CY: Boy in Tall Grasses, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 429LY: Child in Pink, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 430LY: Young Girl, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 1004RY: Simone in a Plumed Hat, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 2180CY: Simone in a White Bonnet, 1987-2003 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 2240CY: Mother and Child in a Landscape, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 3513CY: The Mirror, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 3514CY: Sara Wearing Her Bonnet and Coat, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 3535CY: Ellen Seated Holding an Apple, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 3669CY: Sara and Her Mother Admiring the Baby, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 4475CY: Fillette en Robe Grosaille, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 4817CY: Mother and Daughter, Both Wearing Large Hats, 1991-1996 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 6012CY: The Fitting, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Cassatt, Mary, 7062CY: Sara and Her Mother with the Baby (No. 1), 1999-2002 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Catherwood, Frederick, 1088JY: New York Harbor, 1981-1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Caucaunier, Jean Denis Antoine, 1290RY: La Toilette des Enfants, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Chalfant, Jefferson David, 4493CY: Study for "A Good Story", 1995 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Chambers, Thomas, 3635CY: Fantasy of View of Hudson at Fishkill, New York, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Champney, James Wells, 1719RY: Garden in Old Deerfield, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Champney, James Wells, 2006RY: Indecision, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Champney, James Wells, 2131CY: In the Forest, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Champney, James Wells, 2213JY: By the Pool, 1988, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Chapin, Bryant, 1327CY: Four Red Apples, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Chapin, Bryant, 2339CY: Still-Life: Plums, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Chapman, John Linton, 2884LY: Claudian Aqueduct, Roman Campagna, circa 1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Chapman, Minerva Josephine, 1607CY: Woman with Hat, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Chapman, Minerva Josephine, 1608LY: Portrait of Elizabeth Nourse, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Chapman, Minerva Josephine, 1609CY: Portrait of Mr. P.J., 1985 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Chapman, Minerva Josephine, 1610CY: Amethyst Beads, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Chase, William Merritt: Woman with Japanese Fan, circa 1981-2004 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 230RY: Portrait of Miss F. Deforest, 1981-1996 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 1434CY: The Japanese Doll, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 1659CY: Mrs. Chase in Prospect Park, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 1894CY: My Daughter Dorothy, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 2231CY: Shinnecock Hills from Canoe Place, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 2233RY: A Stormy Day at Bath Beach, Long Island, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 2515CY: Still Life with Samovar, Teapot and Fruit, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 2902LY: The Arno - Florence, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 3282CY: Pulling for Shore, 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 3581CY: At Play, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 3644RY: A Study of My Hound, "Kuttie", 1992 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 4080CY: Dune at Shinnecock, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 6339RY: Shinnecock Landscape, 1996-2002 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Chase, William Merritt, 6877CY: A Study in Curves, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Chatterton, 4319LY: Country Landscape, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Christy, Howard, 6614CY: Chesapeake Bay Landscape, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Church, Frederic Edwin: The Charter Oak, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Church, Frederic Edwin, 1107CY: Twilight on a Winter Landscape, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Church, Frederic Edwin, 1122CY: Evening Star, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Church, Frederic Edwin, 3402CY: Jamaica, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Church, Frederic Edwin, 4332CY: Sunset, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Church, Frederic Edwin, 5019aCY: Study for "The Parthenon", 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Church, Frederic Edwin, 5019bCY: The Erechtheum, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Church, Frederic Edwin, 6021CY: Los Cordilleras, 1997, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Church, Frederic Edwin, 6851CY: Bee Craft Mountain from Church's Farm, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Church, Frederic Edwin, 7733CY: October Landscape, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Churchill, William Worcester, 7735CY: The Letter, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Cimiotti, Gustave, 7464CY: At Devonshire Dock, Bermuda, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Cimiotti, Gustave, 7465CY: A Bermuda Home, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Cimiotti, Gustave, 7515CY: A Hot Day, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Cimiotti, Gustave, 7516CY: The Flower Farm, Bermuda, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Clark, Eliot Candee, 6871CY: Fire - Lower East Side, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Clark, Eliot [Candee], 6882CY: Hillside Cottage, 1998-1999, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Clark, Eliot Candee, 6883CY: Village in Winter, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Clark, Louise Miller, 8987RY: Receding Planes, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Clarke, Sarah F., 5053CY: In the North Carolina Mountains at Waynesville, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Clements, Gabrielle de Veaux, 3415CY: Landscape, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Clinedinst, Benjamin West, 2627CY: By the Fire, 1989, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Clute, Walter M., 4928JY: An Old Dutch Stoop, Schenectady, New York, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Cockcroft, Edith Varian, 4030CY: Winter in Washington Square Park, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Codman, Charles, 1528CY: The Pirate's Retreat, 1985-1988 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Codman, Charles, 2143JY: The Pirate's Retreat, 1986-2000 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Colby, Josephine Wood, 2897RY: The Music Party, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Cole, Joseph Foxcroft, 8991CY: Still Life of Flowers, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Cole, Thomas, 1581CY: View Near Volterra, Italy, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Cole, Thomas, 1661CY: Tree in the Catskills, 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Cole, Thomas, 6568RY: Study for "Catskill Creek", 1998 (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 1387CY: Landscape with Two Women, 1984, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 1483CY: Capri Landscape, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 1593LY: The Villa Castello, Capri, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 1803CY: Azaleas and Apple Blossoms, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 2461RY: Anacapri, 1988, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 2795LY: The Villa Castello, Capri, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 2885LY: Interior (Il Bargello, Florence), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 2886LY: On the Grand Canal, Venice, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 2887LY: Azaleas and Apple Blossoms, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 2904CY: Serenade, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 3190CY: Capri Landscape, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Coleman, Charles Caryl, 4759CY: Still Life with Apple Blossoms, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Coleman, Michael: Winter Evening, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Colman, Samuel, 1460CY: Niagara Falls, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Colman, Samuel, 1624CY: Cambus Kenneth Abbey, Stirling, Scotland, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Colman, Samuel, 1900CY: Franconia Mountains, New Hampshire, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Colman, Samuel, 2354CY: Landscape, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Colman, Samuel, 2676JY: Summer Landscape, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Colman, Samuel, 3697CY: Emigrant Train Fording Medicine, 1992-1995 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Colman, Samuel, 3819CY: Rocky Oceanside, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Colman, Samuel, 6845CY: Mt. Washington, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Cone, Marvin Dorwart, 1558LY: Big Bend, 1985, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Cook, Edith Wilkinson, 2009CY: Mountain Landscape, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Cook, Edith Wilkinson, 2762CY: Autumn, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Cook, Edith Wilkinson, 3038RY: Autumn, 1990, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Cook, Howard, 2597RY: Fisher Huts - Deer Isle, 1988, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Cook, Howard, 3929JY: Rockefeller Center, 1993-1998 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Cook, Howard, 4193RY: Skyscrapers, 1994, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Cook, Howard, 4771CY: Mexican Interior, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Cookman, Charles Edwin, 2189RY: Noon Lunch, 1987, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Cooper, Colin Campbell, 4063CY: Mountains of Manhattan, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Cooper, Colin Campbell, 4932CY: Summer Verandah, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Cooper, Colin Campbell, 8494CY: View in Brittany, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Cooper, Colin Campbell, 8507CY: 42nd Street Library, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Cope, George, 1424CY: Union Mementos, 1984-1995 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Cope, George, 3576LY: Union Mementos on a Door, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Cope, George, 3595CY: Shotgun and Game, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Copley, John Singleton: Mrs. John Stevens (Judith Sargent, later Mrs. John Marray), 1999 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Copley, John Singleton, 2693RY: Sketch for "The Copley Family", 1974, 1986-1991 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Copley, John Singleton, 6119CY: Portrait of Mrs. George Turner, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Corcos, Lucille, 6120CY: Suburban Christmas, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Cornell, Joseph, 2317CY: Nocturne, 1958, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Cornell, Joseph, 2318CY: Mathematics in Nature, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Cornell, Joseph, 2538CY: Untitled (Soap Bubble Set), 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Cornoyer, Paul, 2297CY: Nocturne, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Costigan, John E., 6121CY: Bringing Home the Christmas Tree, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Couse, Eanger Irving, 3545RY: Roasting Corn, 1992, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Couse, Eanger Irving, 3998CY: On the Seine, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Couse, Eanger Irving, 4806CY: Roasting Corn, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Cowell, [William Wilson], 1705CY: Sunset Off Bellport, Long Island, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Cox, Kenyon, 7649LY: Autumn Sunshine, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Cozzens, [Frederick Schiller], 4328LY: On the New England Coast, 1994-1995, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Craig, Thomas Bigelow, 1207CY: Summer Morn, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Craig, Thomas Bigelow, 4240CY: The Lovers and The Conversation (Pair), 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Cramer, Konrad, 2257RY: Doors - Window and Hall, 1988, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Cramer, Konrad, 2686CY: Still Life: Roses in a Vase, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Cramer, Konrad, 3054CY: Still Life with Black Stone, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Cramer, Konrad, 3055CY: Poppies in White Vase, 1990-1995 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Cramer, Konrad, 3056CY: Nasturtium with Green Vase, 1990-1994 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Cramer, Konrad, 3350CY: Bread Board and Silver Knife, 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Cramer, Konrad, 3899CY: Patches and Son, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Cramer, Konrad, 4042CY: Improvisation, Orange Movement, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Cramer, Konrad, 4178CY: Abstraction, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Crane, Bruce, 4594CY: Spring Gladness, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Crane, Bruce, 4595CY: Woods at Sunset, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Crane, Bruce, 4618CY: A Landscape, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Crane, Bruce, 8502CY: After a Shower, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Crane, Stanley Edwin William, 6134CY: Oystercatcher, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 237CY: Nassau I, 1981-1988 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 1421CY: Industrial Abstraction, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 1632CY: Still Life with Pineapple and Egg, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 1849CY: Overseas Highway, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 2316CY: St. Louis Cemetery, 1988-1994 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 4642CY: Twisted Objects on the Deck, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 4993CY: Study for Fisherman's Wharf, San Francisco, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 7073CY: Boats, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 7074CY: Tanks, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 7075CY: Grey Street, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 8937CY: Overseas Highway, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 8938CY: Third Avenue Elevated No. 1, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 8983CY: Tanks, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - Criss, Francis, 850CY: Surrealist Collage, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Criss, Francis, 851CY: Impression of New York Street, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Criss, Francis, 1132RY: Study, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Criss, Francis, 1133RY: Study for the Third Avenue El, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Criss, Francis, 2216CY: Tulips, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - Criss, Francis, 2472RY: Indian Theme, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Criss, Francis, 3431CY: Portrait of Jill Becker, 1991-1996 (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - Crocker, John Denison, 4356CY: Family of Settlers Moving Thru a Landscape, 1994-1997 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 1320CY: The Setting Sun, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 1686CY: Winter in Switzerland, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 1835CY: Autumn Landscape, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 2736CY: Landscape in Early Fall, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 3111CY: Lake Landscape, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 3394LY: Sportsmen Nooning, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 3418CY: Lake Scene, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 4132CY: Landscape in Early Fall, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 4345CY: Boaters on a Lake, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 4458CY: Autumn in the Highland of the Hudson, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 7043CY: Indian Summer at the Hudson Highlands, 1998-2004 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 7681JY: In the Wyoming Valley, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 7740RY: Summer Landscape, 2001, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 9414CY: Early Snow on Mount Washington, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Cross, Henry H., 2677CY: Indian Encampment, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Cross, Henry H., 3997CY: The Old Union Race Course, Long Island, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Cross, Henry H., 8489CY: On the Track, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 13)